## Kira Kirson

Gameplay Designer

Kiradkirson@gmail.com (858) 413 - 5171 <a href="https://kirakirson.github.io">https://kirakirson.github.io</a> 9706 221st St SE Snohomish, WA

### **Summary**

Extremely flexible and self-motivated designer with a diverse background in both art and programming. Strong understanding of all aspects of the game development process with 6 years of experience designing games as personal and professional projects. Positive team player with a dedication to collaborating and improving to make each project the best that it can be.

### Skills

- Confident with a wide variety of game engines, such as Unity, Unreal Engine 5, and Godot
- Expertise in OOP in C#, Unreal Blueprinting, C++, JavaScript, and Python, with a high aptitude for learning new languages
- Well-accustomed to communicating in a cross-discipline team, as well as working independently in a fast-paced work environment
- Familiar with GitHub, Perforce and source control software
- Understands the requirements and limitations of a wide range of consoles and hardware
- Manual testing and debugging experience with bug tracking software
- Experience working in the Scrum and Agile project management workflow
- Passionate about accessibility in gaming

## **Experience**

### **TEKSystems | Redmond WA United States - Technical Tester** Aug 2023 - May 2024

- Tested compatibility for Nintendo, giving experience with Nintendo Switch requirements and guidelines
- Made swift decisions about issues of quality and usability
- Excelled in an independent, fast paced work environment
- Communicated progress and questions with a large team both online and in person while strictly adhering to NDA

# BrickRed Systems | Redmond WA United States - Accessibility Tester Oct 2020 - Jul 2023

- Highly ranked game tester, with experience mentoring new team members
- Followed detailed testing procedures efficiently and carefully
- Identified and completed precise and accurate bug reports
- Team member for Microsoft's Gaming Accessibility Testing Service, giving extensive knowledge of the Xbox Accessibility Guidelines
- Ensured compliance with strict NDA

#### **Health Nuts Media | United States - Contract Coder**

Oct 2020 - Aug 2022

- Updated the Huff&Puff app which helps children manage and learn about their asthma
- Took a broken existing app and rebuilt it with a much newer version of Unity
- Communicated remotely with clients and met deadlines with little oversight

## **Education**

### Savannah College of Art and Design | Savannah, GA

Interactive Design and Game Development, Bachelor of Arts Aug 2016 - May 2020

### Poway High School | Poway, CA

High School Diploma Aug 2012 - May 2016